# GARY MCKEEVER

SOFTWARE DEVELOPER \$\scrick\$ 2182906677

#### • DETAILS •

2182906677 <a href="mailto:shephard@frostbytn.com">shephard@frostbytn.com</a>

• LINKS •

LinkedIn

**GitHub** 

**Resume Online** 

• SKILLS •

C#

TypeScript

JS, HTML, CSS

Python

SQL

C++

LINO

No-SQL

WPF

Node.js

REST API

**Database Architecture** 

**Inductive Reasoning** 

Embedded IoT

**Full Stack Development** 

Microsoft Azure

**SQL Server Management** 

Linux

**Version Repository** 

**Project Coordination** 

## PROFILE

Software developer with a diversified skill set going on 5 years of experience. Has a knack for creative problem solving and quickly learning new frameworks and environments. Looking for an opportunity to create unique and impacting solutions for today's problems.

#### EMPLOYMENT HISTORY

### Software Developer at Northeast Technical Services

2016 - 2021

- Identify issues and develop solutions by writing custom software and databases.
- Maintain existing company software by debugging, testing, and adding feature requests.
- Create software to visualize and interpret data generated by company applications.
- Design understandable UI/UX for company staff and clients.

## Pharmacy Technician, Inventory Manager at CVS Pharmacy

2015 - 2017

- Worked quickly and efficiently despite the strict control of HIPPA, DEA, Board of Pharmacy, and company Best Practices.
- Learned and implemented CVS Inventory system practices and procedures for team
- Provided system assistance to other team members during CVS conversion.

# Pharmacy Technician, Barista at Target Corporation

2011 - 2015

- Studied and tested out of Target's Pharmacy Licensure Exams recognized by Minnesota.
- Given Inventory Management role in 2014 to reduce product overhead and expired drugs on shelf.
- Cross trained in most of Target and assisted team whenever and wherever possible.

#### EDUCATION

# Computer Science, University of Minnesota - Duluth

2014 - 2017

Coursework included CS I & II, Software Analysis and Design, IT in Business, and Software Engineering.

## Business Administration Mnr, University of Minnesota - Duluth

2021 - 2021

Coursework included MIS, Accounting, Statistics, and Marketing.

## Associate of Arts, Mesabi Range Community and Technical College

2007 - 2010

HS Diploma, Eveleth - Gilbert High School

2007

## ¶ REFERENCES

Available upon request